gnolia.com 2009-11-12

# Gnolia: Privacy Policy

At Gnolia Systems, we are committed to protecting your privacy. We love to use the web as much as you, and so we’ve used the ‘do unto others’ rule to set up the privacy safeguards that we discuss below.

We use the information we collect about you on the Gnolia web site is used to build our tag suggestion system, allow you to identify yourself when communicating with Gnolia members or groups, and for us to communicate with you about the Gnolia site and in any newsletters you have opted into. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.

## What information does Gnolia collect on its web site? How do we use it?

When you sign-up for a Gnolia free account, we ask for your email address, screen name, password and some limited information about your geographic location, age and gender. We just use this information to make Gnolia a better product for you.

While you are using the Gnolia service, Gnolia stores all data that you have saved, including saved bookmarks and applied tags so that we can maintain your collection and keep it distinct from everyone else’s.

## How does Gnolia Systems protect customer information?

When you provide information or log into a protected area on the Gnolia web site, we use a secure server. This secure server software, SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all of the transactional data we collect is protected against unauthorized access with the use of digital certificates. Digital certificates for Gnolia Systems are issued by VeriSign, one of the most established signers of digital certificates. To learn more about our online security, simply click on the “Security” icon (it usually appears as a padlock) in your browser tool bar, at the bottom of your browser window. If you do not see an indication of secure mode where you think it should be, then contact us immediately to let us know.

## Will Gnolia Systems disclose the information it collects to outside parties?

Absolutely not. Gnolia Systems will not sell, trade or rent the individualized and personal information you submit without your express permission – period. Gnolia Systems may provide aggregate statistics about our users, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information. That means we may talk about what happens with large numbers of users on our system, but we never share data about individual users.

If any part of this privacy policy gives you concern, we invite you to discuss it with us by using our contact form. We will update this policy in the future to make its terms more clear when necessary, and to respond to changes in legal and public thinking about privacy online.
